[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Procedural Memory, a category of the long-term memory, refers to which of these basic human abilities?", "correct_answer": "The ability to acquire and develop skills", "incorrect_answers": ["The ability to gain and store general knowledge and information", "The ability to consciously retrieve stored facts and information", "The artistic and creative abilities"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film High School Musical, Ms. Darbus tells a seamstress to add what?", "correct_answer": "gold", "incorrect_answers": ["shimmer", "ribbon", "glitter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2006 movie Little Miss Sunshine was co-produced by Marc Turtletaub. Which company did he found before becoming a movie producer?", "correct_answer": "The Money Store", "incorrect_answers": ["Wentworth Financial", "Geek Squad", "Ask Jeeves, Inc."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Oscar-winning movie Dances With Wolves ran over budget and Kevin Costner was forced to make up the overages personally.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shinsengumi group remained loyal to the Tokugawa shogunate until the end of the Bakamatsu.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pictures on a web page can be stored in more than one physical location.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scientist is believed to have been the first true alchemist in Medieval Europe, as well as the most significant?", "correct_answer": "Roger Bacon", "incorrect_answers": ["Isaac Newton", "Thomas Aquinas", "Galileo Galilei"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Each basic taste corresponds to a specific area of the tongue, which perceives it. This spacial division of taste receptors is called taste map.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which US state means large creek in the Seneca language?", "correct_answer": "Ohio", "incorrect_answers": ["Idaho", "Texas", "Wisconsin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the female lead in The Conversation?", "correct_answer": "Cindi Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Sally Fields", "Goldie  Hawn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Slow motion is is a technique in filmmaking most commonly referred to as what?", "correct_answer": "Overcranking", "incorrect_answers": ["Undercranking", "Reversedcranking", "Fastcranking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marijuana is produced from parts of the male cannabis plants.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]